revtrak.net 2014-08-13

# RevTrak - Privacy Policy | Online Processing Security | K12 School & City Payment Solutions

## Scope of This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers RevTrak’s treatment of personally identifiable information collected from customers (hereafter "customer" or "you") who use the RevTrak payment services, as well as consumer information that we acquire in the course of our business. This Policy also covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that RevTrak business partners may share with RevTrak. 

This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that RevTrak does not own or control or to people that RevTrak does not employ or manage. 

## Information Collection and Use

In the course of processing a payment transaction, we receive information about the payment that a consumer has furnished in placing the order. 

The personally identifiable information we acquire in processing payment transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which you are using our payment services. It may include, but is not limited to, the amount of the transaction, the consumer's name, credit card number and expiration date, billing address, and shipping address. 

RevTrak uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the merchant services. We may also send you service announcements, newsletters, and periodic notices about new products or services. Personally identifiable consumer information is used to process payment transactions, assist you with customer service and marketing your services and for no other purposes. RevTrak does not store credit card numbers in its shopping cart software. 

RevTrak does not offer services or sell products to children. RevTrak does not request or knowingly collect personally identifiable contact information from anyone under the age of 13. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Protecting personally identifiable information about merchants and consumers is an important part of our business. We share and disclose such information only as described below. 

RevTrak will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

  1. we have your consent to share the information;
  2. we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  3. we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of RevTrak to provide a product or service to you (unless we tell you differently these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide them beyond what is necessary to assist us).

Personally identifiable consumer information is shared with third parties (such as banks and credit card processors) to the extent necessary for RevTrak to deliver payment processing services. 

We also may release personally identifiable information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Merchant Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of RevTrak, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and risk reduction. 

In the unlikely event that RevTrak is acquired, merchant account information may be one of the transferred assets. 

## Information Security

Information security is critical to our business. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We store information gathered on secure computers located in a locked data center. The number of employees involved in the management of the data center that have physical access to these computers is limited. We use firewalls and other security technology to prevent our computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons. 

We also require that any personally identifiable consumer card holder information sent to us by you be encrypted using SSL encryption. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your Login ID/password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and otherwise protect the password used to access the RevTrak services. 

## Account Information and Preferences

RevTrak gives you the ability to edit your RevTrak Account Information and preferences at any time by using the Web Store Intranet Settings, or by contacting us via our [E-Z Help online portal](http://ezhelp.revtrak.com/helpspot/). 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

RevTrak reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. If there are material changes to this statement or in how RevTrak will use personally identifiable information, RevTrak will post notice on the RevTrak news release page at www.RevTrak.com prior to implementing the change.
